大家好，欢迎观看今天的节目。
今天我们要讨论一个非常有趣的话题。
小明：你觉得这个方案怎么样？
小红：我觉得还不错，但是需要一些改进。
特别是在用户体验方面。
好的，我们继续。
这是一条非常非常非常非常非常非常非常非常长的句子，用来测试长行检测功能是否正常工作。
这行也
有两行
还有第三行
第四行
大家好，欢迎观看今天的节目。
今天我们要讨论一个非常有趣的话题。
小明：你觉得这个方案怎么样？
小红：我觉得还不错，但是需要一些改进。
特别是在用户体验方面。
好的，我们继续。
这是一条非常非常非常非常非常非常非常非常长的句子，用来测试长行检测功能是否正常工作。
这行也
有两行
还有第三行
第四行
张三：今天天气真好啊。
李四：是啊，我们出去走走吧。
王五：好主意，我正想出去活动活动。
张三：那我们去公园怎么样？
李四：我觉得可以，那里风景不错。
Welcome to our video tutorial.
In this lesson, we will learn about subtitle processing.
It's a very useful skill for translators.
Let's start with the basics.
First, we need to understand the subtitle formats.
Welcome to our video tutorial.
In this lesson, we will learn about subtitle processing.
It's a very useful skill for translators.
Let's start with the basics.
First, we need to understand the subtitle formats.
This cue has multiple lines.
Line two is here.
Line three too.
This cue has an ID before the timestamp.